const questions = [

    {
        question: "What type of equipment resides at Layer 1 of the OSI model? (Select all that apply)",
        options: ["Router", "Hub", "Switch", "Network cabling", "Repeater"],
        answer: ["Hub", "Network cabling", "Repeater"]
    },
    {
        question: "Examples of common protocols that reside at the OSI Transport Layer include: (Select 2 answers)",
        options: ["UDP", "IP", "HTTPS", "ICMP", "TCP", "ARP"],
        answer: ["UDP", "TCP"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the answers listed below refers to a unique, 48-bit identifier also known as a physical network address?",
        options: ["SSID", "IP", "GUID", "MAC"],
        answer: ["MAC"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following devices reside(s) at the Data Link Layer of the OSI model? (Select all that apply)",
        options: ["Bridge", "Media converter", "Switch", "Hub", "Network adapter"],
        answer: ["Bridge", "Switch", "Network adapter"]
    },
    {
        question: "The term 'Presentation Layer' is used in reference to:",
        options: ["Layer 7 of the OSI model", "Layer 5 of the OSI model", "Layer 6 of the OSI model", "Layer 4 of the OSI model"],
        answer: ["Layer 6 of the OSI model"]
    },
    {
        question: "In the OSI model, the protocol data unit at the Physical Layer is known as:",
        options: ["Segment", "Frame", "Bit", "Packet", "Datagram"],
        answer: ["Bit"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which OSI layer assumes responsibility for opening, closing, and maintaining connections between applications?",
        options: ["Network Layer", "Data Link Layer", "Application Layer", "Session Layer"],
        answer: ["Session Layer"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the devices listed below is often referred to as a multilayer switch?",
        options: ["Router", "Media converter", "Bridge", "Transceiver"],
        answer: ["Router"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following protocols reside at the Application Layer of the OSI model? (Select 3 answers)",
        options: ["ARP", "HTTP", "FTP", "IP", "SMTP", "TCP/UDP"],
        answer: ["HTTP", "FTP", "SMTP"]
    },
    {
        question: "In the OSI model, the Data Link Layer is also known as:",
        options: ["Layer 3", "Layer 1", "Layer 5", "Layer 2"],
        answer: ["Layer 2"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the answers listed below refer to common network protocols that reside at Layer 3 of the OSI model? (Select 2 answers)",
        options: ["ICMP", "SIP", "IP", "ARP", "SNMP"],
        answer: ["ICMP", "IP"]
    },
    {
        question: "In the OSI model, the Layer 4 UDP protocol data unit is called:",
        options: ["Bit", "Frame", "Packet", "Segment", "Datagram"],
        answer: ["Datagram"]
    },
    {
        question: "Layer 2 of the OSI model is also referred to as:",
        options: ["Transport Layer", "Network Layer", "Data Link Layer", "Physical Layer"],
        answer: ["Data Link Layer"]
    },
    {
        question: "Data format translation, data compression, and data encryption/decryption take place at the:",
        options: ["Application Layer of the OSI model", "Presentation Layer of the OSI model", "Session Layer of the OSI model", "Transport Layer of the OSI model"],
        answer: ["Presentation Layer of the OSI model"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following answers refers to Layer 1 of the OSI model?",
        options: ["Transport Layer", "Physical Layer", "Application Layer", "Data Link Layer"],
        answer: ["Physical Layer"]
    },
    {
        question: "The term 'Application Layer' is used in reference to:",
        options: ["Layer 6 of the OSI model", "Layer 4 of the OSI model", "Layer 7 of the OSI model", "Layer 5 of the OSI model"],
        answer: ["Layer 7 of the OSI model"]
    },
    {
        question: "In the OSI reference model, a NIC resides at the:",
        options: ["Physical Layer", "Data Link Layer", "Network Layer", "Transport Layer"],
        answer: ["Data Link Layer"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the OSI layers listed below is also known as the Session Layer?",
        options: ["Layer 6", "Layer 3", "Layer 5", "Layer 2"],
        answer: ["Layer 5"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following devices resides at the Network Layer of the OSI model?",
        options: ["Switch", "Repeater", "Bridge", "Router"],
        answer: ["Router"]
    },
    {
        question: "In the OSI model, the Layer 2 protocol data unit is known as:",
        options: ["Bit", "Frame", "Packet", "Segment", "Datagram"],
        answer: ["Frame"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which OSI layer enables direct interaction between the end-user and the network?",
        options: ["Layer 5", "Layer 1", "Layer 7", "Layer 3"],
        answer: ["Layer 7"]
    },
    {
        question: "In the OSI model, the Network Layer protocol data unit is called:",
        options: ["Bit", "Frame", "Packet", "Segment", "Datagram"],
        answer: ["Packet"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the answers listed below refers to a common OSI Layer 2 protocol?",
        options: ["HTTP", "IP", "ARP", "ICMP"],
        answer: ["ARP"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following answers refers to Layer 6 of the OSI model?",
        options: ["Data Link Layer", "Application Layer", "Presentation Layer", "Session Layer"],
        answer: ["Presentation Layer"]
    }
];